- Outta my way, you
psychedelic space junk!
- 别挡我的路，你
迷幻的太空垃圾！
Sweet Neptune!
甜蜜的海王星！
Have I found the
beginning of the universe?
我找到了吗
宇宙的开始？
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
- Ooh!
- 哦！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- ♪ Who lives a
pineapple under the sea? ♪
- ♪ 谁住在
海底的菠萝？ ♪
all: Grandpat Sea Star!
全体：海星爷爷！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all: Grandpat Sea Star!
全体：海星爷爷！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all: Grandpat Sea Star!
全体：海星爷爷！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: Grandpat Sea Star!
- Ready?
全体：海星爷爷！
- 准备好？
all: Grandpat Sea Star!
Grandpat Sea Star!
全体：海星爷爷！
海星爷爷！
Grandpat Sea Star!
Grandpat
爷爷
Sea Star!
- Oh! Ow!
海星！
- 哦！噢！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[dentures clicking
rhythmically]
[假牙咔哒声
有节奏地]
Ow!
噢！
I gotta get out
of this nightmare!
我得出去
这个噩梦！
[gasps] Ohh!
[喘气]哦！
[shimmering tone]
[闪烁的音调]
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
[intense Western music]
【强烈的西洋音乐】
♪ ♪
- [spits]
- [吐口水]
♪ ♪
- [spits]
- [吐口水]
- This town ain't big enough
for the both of us.
- 这个城镇不够大
为了我们俩。
[electricity crackles]
[电流爆裂声]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- Whoa!
- Ahh!
- 哇！
- 啊！
Ohh!
哦！
[electricity crackles]
[电流爆裂声]
- [munching]
- [咀嚼]
- Um--this town ain't big
enough for the both of us.
- 嗯——这个小镇不大
对我们俩来说足够了。
[gong splash]
[锣声四溅]
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
- Now that's
a good looking baby!
- 现在就是这样
一个好看的宝贝！
- [neighs]
- [嘶嘶声]
- Well, this is my stop.
- 嗯，这是我的站。
See y'all later!
稍后见！
Hyep!
Giddy-up, now!
嗨！
头晕目眩，现在！
- [neighs]
- Yahoo!
- [嘶嘶声]
- 雅虎！
- Happy trails!
- 快乐的足迹！
[electricity zapping]
Ahh!
[电击]
啊！
Ohh!
哦！
[crashing]
[崩溃]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Uh! Yah!
呃！啊！
[playing Polka music]
[演奏波尔卡音乐]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Bonjour.
- 你好。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
It's good to be back home
where it's normal.
回到家真好
这是正常的。
- Hi, Grandpat--
- Huh?
-嗨，爷爷--
- 啊？
- What you watching?
- 你在看什么？
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
Ehh, close enough.
呃，够接近了。
- And so we leave things
a little bit weird,
- 所以我们留下东西
有点奇怪，
but that's how we like it
here in "The Tidal Zone."
但这就是我们喜欢的方式
这里是“潮汐区”。
Au revoir.
再见。
[static buzzing]
- Hey, I was watching that!
[静电嗡嗡声]
- 嘿，我正在看那个！